<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webinar_details on jomresearch</title>
    <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webinar_details on jomresearch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro to R (for non-coders)</title>
      <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-10-12-intro-to-r-for-non-coders/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-10-12-intro-to-r-for-non-coders/</guid>
      <description>The material for this webinar is available for purchase:
 Title: Intro to R (for non-coders) Language: English Price: RM50 (7 hour recording, slides, dummy data, and R codes/scripts) Content:  Flow of data analysis R, RStudio, and Posit Installation, updates, and R packages Data types in R Indexing and data wrangling Identifying missing values and duplicates Descriptive statistics Basic plots Hands-on   Click to buy  Go to past webinars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An introduction to SPSS &amp; JAMOVI</title>
      <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-29-an-introduction-to-spss-jamovi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-29-an-introduction-to-spss-jamovi/</guid>
      <description>The recording and slides of this webinar is available for purchase:
 Title: An introduction to SPSS &amp;amp; jamovi Language: English Price: RM30 (recording, slides, and dummy data used in the webinar will be provided) Content:  Basic functionalities of the software Data exploration Flow of data analysis Descriptive statistics Basic plots Hands-on using both software (practical step-by-step)   Click to buy  Go to past webinars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to conduct a systematic review</title>
      <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-10-how-to-conduct-a-systematic-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-10-how-to-conduct-a-systematic-review/</guid>
      <description>The recording and slides of this webinar is available for purchase:
 Title: How to conduct a systematic review Language: English Price: RM80 (recording, slides, and e-certificate are included) Content:  What is a systematic review Type of review papers Step by step of conducting a systematic review:  Developing a review protocol Protocol registration Search terms Search strategies Screening strategies Critical appraisal tools   Writing a systematic review paper:  PRISMA and other guidelines Result presentation Example of not a good systematic review     Click to buy  Go to past webinars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to publish a paper for beginners and newbies (for health sciences)</title>
      <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-07-how-to-publish-a-paper-for-beginners-and-newbies-for-health-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-07-how-to-publish-a-paper-for-beginners-and-newbies-for-health-sciences/</guid>
      <description>The recording and slides of this webinar is available for purchase:
 Title: How to publish a paper for beginners and newbies (for health sciences) Language: English Price: RM10 Content:  Why publish a paper? Indexing databases? Publishers vs journals Predatory publishers and journals How to find a journal? Open access vs closed access Peer review Cover letter Reviewer suggestion   Click here to buy  Go to past webinars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to read a paper for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-07-how-to-read-a-paper-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-07-how-to-read-a-paper-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>The recording and slides of this webinar is available for purchase:
 Title: How to read a paper for beginners Language: English Price: RM10 Content:  Why read a paper? Types of research paper Where to find a paper Sections in a paper Critical appraisal tools Steps (my way) in reading a paper How to use AI in reading a paper   Click here to buy  Go to past webinars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write a scientific paper for beginners (for health sciences)</title>
      <link>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-07-how-to-write-a-scientific-paper-for-beginners-for-health-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jomresearch.netlify.app/webinar_detail/2023-09-07-how-to-write-a-scientific-paper-for-beginners-for-health-sciences/</guid>
      <description>The recording and slides of this webinar is available for purchase:
 Title: How to write a scientific paper for beginners (for health sciences) Language: English Price: RM30 Content:  Why write a paper? Types of a scientific paper General flow of a scientific paper Write-up plan/protocol Anatomy of a scientific paper Flow of writing (my own) Extra tips for a write-up Reference manager - Mendeley/Zotero Use of AI in a write-up (my opinion)   Click here to buy  Go to past webinars</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
