<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jomresearch</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jomresearch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 01:15:29 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Jom Research, is an academic consultant platform owned by TMH Research Kits Resources (SSM registration no: 202303206919), a company based in Malaysia. Jom Research was founded with the specific purpose of offering easily accessible webinars centered around research and statistical analysis at a reasonable price point. What sets Jom Research apart is its commitment to providing a comprehensive learning journey, starting from the foundational basics and progressing seamlessly to more advanced topics in the realm of research and statistical analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>temas</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/categoria/temas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:21:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/categoria/temas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sintaxe</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/categoria/sintaxe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:21:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/categoria/sintaxe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Códigos curtos</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 11:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/tags/shortcodes/_index.pt-br/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultation</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/consultation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/consultation/</guid>
      <description>We have yet to provide any consultation services at the moment. Stay tuned and follow us on Facebook for more info 😊.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Message or email us at:  Link to heading   Facebook page: Jom Research Email: jom.research.malaysia@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trainers</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/trainers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/trainers/</guid>
      <description>Lead academic trainer:  Link to heading    Name: Tengku Muhammad Hanis Bin Tengku Mokhtar Education:  PhD student (Public Health Epidemiology, USM) MSc (Medical Statistics, USM) MBBCh (Al-Azhar University)   Experience:  Successfully run several workshops on bibliometric analysis, systematic reviews, and meta-analysis Published more than fifteen papers in Web of Science- and Scopus-indexed journal   Research interest:  Medical statistics, systematic review, bibliometrics, meta-analysis Machine learning, deep learning, text analysis R and Python application in medical research    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webinars</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/webinars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/webinars/</guid>
      <description>Below are the list of our webinars.
Future webinars:  Link to heading      Webinar title Date Fee Link to register     How to write a paper for beginners Yet to be decided RM30 Stay tuned   How to do a systematic review Yet to be decided RM70 Stay tuned   How to do a bibliometric analysis Yet to be decided RM70 Stay tuned   How to read a meta-analysis paper Yet to be decided RM50 Stay tuned   An introduction to R Yet to be decided RM40 Stay tuned   How to do a meta-analysis Yet to be decided RM70 Stay tuned   Simple numerical analysis using R Yet to be decided RM100 Stay tuned   Simple categorical analysis using R Yet to be decided RM100 Stay tuned   Machine learning using R Yet to be decided RM100 Stay tuned    Past webinars:  Link to heading   (The recordings and slides are available for purchase)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
